Guide to the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection RG.11.4
New York University Archives
- Series XI: Building files: Washington Square Center
  - Deutsches Haus [42 Washington Mews]-- Programs, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Division of General Education -- Space Allocation, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - East Building, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - East Building, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - East Building, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - East Building, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - East Building -- Institute for Developmental Studies, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - East Building -- Inst. for Dev. Studies, Center for Deafness Rehab., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Education Building, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Education Building, 1965-1972 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Education Building -- Art Studio, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Education Building -- Art Studio, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Education Building -- Art Studio, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Education Building -- Auditorium, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Education Building -- Auditorium, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Education Building (Proposed), 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Education Building (Proposed), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Education Building (Proposed), 1963-1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Education Building/Center (Proposed)-- Construction Grant App., 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Education Building/Center (Proposed)-- Loan, Grant Application, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Education, School of -- Space Planning, 1961-1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Eighth Street -- Proposed Administration Bldg., Dorm. Zoning, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Eighth Street -- Zoning, 1969-1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 10 East Eighth Street -- Pants Pub Store, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 22 East Eighth Street [Corner University Place], undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Elevator Data, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Farkas Hall/School of Education-Social Work Bldg. (Proposed), 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Farkas Hall/School of Education-Social Work Bldg. (Proposed) -- Space Data Sheets, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Farkas Hall/School of Education-Social Work Bldg. (Proposed), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - One Fifth Avenue -- Chancellor=s Residence, School Continuing Education, Modern Language Assoc. Facilities (Proposed), 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 11 Fifth Avenue, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 55 Fifth Avenue -- Division of General Education, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 60 Fifth Avenue & area -- Div. of General Education (Proposed), 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 70 Fifth Avenue, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 545 Fifth Avenue -- Development Office, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Film Theater (Proposed) [69-71 W. Third St.]--School of the Arts, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Founders Monument, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - 15-19 West Fourth Street, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Gould Plaza, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - 242 Greene Street, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Grosvenor Residence Hall, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Hayden Hall, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Hayden Hall -- Cafeteria -- Specifications, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Hayden Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Hayden Hall, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Hayden Hall -- Sketched, notes, misc., undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Health Services -- Relocation, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Housing - General, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Interior Design -- Leeds Associates Program, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Jewish Cultural Center (Proposed), 1960-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Judson Hall -- General, Proposed Usage, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Judson Hall -- Planning, Progress Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Judson Hall -- Roberto Notebook, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Judson Hall -- Landmarks/Historic Preservation, 1966-1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Judson Hall -- News Clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Judson Hall -- Retention of Roberto, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Judson Hall -- Area Measurements, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Judson Hall -- Budget, Expenses, 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Judson Hall -- Doors, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Judson Hall -- Electrical, Alarm, Sprinklers, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Judson Hall -- Funding, 1974-1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Judson Hall -- Ironwork, Steps (Exterior), 1974-1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Judson Hall -- Masonry (Exterior), 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Judson Hall -- Painting, Carpets, Tile, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Judson Hall -- Plumbing, Heating, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Judson Hall -- Roof, Cross, Tower, Birdproofing, 1974-1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Judson Hall -- Structural, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Judson Hall -- Windows, 1974-May 1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Judson Hall -- Windows, Jun 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1976 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1977 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South], 1979-1987, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South] -- Specifications, 1978, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Wash. Sq. So.] -- News Clippings, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Wash. Sq. So.] -- Drawings, Floor Plans, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Kevorkian Center [50 Washington Square South] -- Brochure, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Kimball Hall, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Kimball Hall, Jan 1963-Aug 1963 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Kimball Hall, Sep 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Kimball Hall, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Landscaping -- including Russell Page Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Landscaping -- Tree Planting -- University Place, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Landscaping -- Tree Planting, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Student Centers at Other Universities, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Architects: Harrison & Abramovitz, etc., 1952-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Furnishings, Equipment, Decorations, 1955-1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Dedication, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Loeb Student Center --General, Lubin Theater Addition (Proposed)1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Loeb Student Center --General, Lubin Theater Addition (Proposed), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Loeb Student Center --General, Lubin Theater Addition (Proposed), 1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Loeb Student Center, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Main Block [Main, Brown, Waverly Buildings], 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Main Block [Main, Brown, Waverly Buildings], 1966, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Main Building, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Main Building, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Main Building, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Main Building, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Main Building, 1966-1974, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Main Building -- Admissions, Bursar, Recorder, Registrar Offices, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Main Building -- Fine Arts Dept., Grey Art Gallery, Art Collection, 1961-1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Main Building -- Library, Music Library, 1962-1966 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Maison Francaise [16 Washington Mews], 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 270 Mercer Street [709 Broadway], 1964 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics -- Meeting Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics -- Meeting Minutes, Jan 1965-Mar 1965 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics -- Meeting Minutes, Mar 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Meyer Hall Of Physics -- Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Moot Court [249 Sullivan Street] C School of Law, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Multiple Buildings/Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Murals and Paintings, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - NYU Buildings -- Greeting Card Depictions by Roberto, others, 1969-1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Press Building and Press Annex, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Print Shop/Office of University Publications, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rubin International Residence Hall [35 Fifth Avenue], 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rufus D. Smith Hall [25 Waverly Place], 1961-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - School of the Arts -- Facility Requirements, Establishment, 1959-1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - School of the Arts -- Facility, Space Requirements, Planning, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - School for Children/Experimental Elementary School (Proposed), 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - School for Children/Experimental Elementary School (Proposed) -- Planning Reports, Meeting Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Science Building (Proposed), 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Science Building/ Life Science Building (Proposed), 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 14, Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 3)
  - Sculpture -- Picasso Sculpture at Silver Towers, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Sculpture -- Charles Poindexter Lions, Vase for Loeb, Medical Ctr, 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Sculpture -- Shakespeare Bust, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Sculpture -- Walt Whitman Statue, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 105 Second Avenue [Fillmore East]-- School of the Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 107 Second Avenue -- School of the Arts, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - 111 Second Avenue [Village Theater, Central Plaza Bldg.] -- SOA, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Shimkin Hall [Commerce Building] -- Signs and Plaques, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Signs and Plaques -- Building Identification/Sign Program, 1964-1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Signs and Plaques, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Signs and Plaques -- NYU Seal, 1964-1973 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Signs and Plaques, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Signs and Plaques -- Higher Education Facilities Act Buildings, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1961 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1963 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1964 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Silver Towers [University Village, University Plaza Towers], 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Silver Towers [UV, UPT] -- Budget, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Silver Towers [UV, UPT] -- News Releases, Clippings, Programs, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Silver Towers [UV, UPT] --Floor Plans, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Silver Towers [UV, UPT] -- Space Studies, Specifications, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Silver Towers [UV, UPT] -- Specifications, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - South Building [51 West Fourth Street], 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - South Building [51 West Fourth Street] -- Communications Arts Group -- TV Studio, Theater, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Southeast/General Classroom Building (Proposed), Jan 1960-Jul 1960 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Southeast/General Classroom Building (Proposed), Aug 1960-Dec 1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Southeast/General Classroom Building (Proposed), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Sports Center (Proposed), 1957-1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Sports Center (Proposed), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sports Center (Proposed), 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Stern Hall [80 Wash. Sq. E., 43-51 W. 4th St.] (Proposed) -- Architect Meeting (WASA) Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Roberto, Misc. Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Construction Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Construction Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Construction Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Budget, Finances, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Inspection, Alterations Certification, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed), 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed), 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Specifications, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Specifications, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Dining Facilities, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Press Kit, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Stern Hall (Proposed) -- Drawings, Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Students Building [80 Washington Square East], 1961-1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 85 West Third Street [Poe House], 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 102 West Third Street -- Law Center Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Tisch Hall, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 12 University Place [Mews Studio], 1962-1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Proposed Building, Zoning Studies, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions Office, Registrar=s Office, 1960-Sep 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions, Div. of General Education, Oct 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions Office, Jan 1963-Jun 1963 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions Office, Fales Collection, Jul 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - 13-19 University Place, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - 13-19 University Place, Jan 1965-Mar 1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - 13-19 University Place, Apr 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - 13-19 University Place, May 1965-Jul 1965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - 13-19 University Place, Aug 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions, Romance Languages, Arts, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions, Entrance, Landscaping, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Admissions, Entrance, Zum Zum Rest., 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - 13-19 University Place -- Fales Library, 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Vanderbilt Hall, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Vanderbilt Hall, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Vanderbilt Hall, 1968-1975 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Vanderbilt Hall -- Sketches for Christmas Card, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Vanderbilt Hall -- Drawings, Floor Plans, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Veg Pac Building -- Proposed Tax Library, Law School Addition, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Natn=l Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Natn=l Science Foundation Grant Proposal, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jan 1962-Mar 1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Apr 1962-Jun 1962 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jul 1962-Aug 1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Sep 1962-Oct 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Nov 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jan 1963-Feb 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Mar 1963-Apr 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, May 1963-Jul 1963 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Aug 1963-Oct 1963 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Nov 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jan 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Feb 1964-Mar 1964 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Apr 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jul 1964-Sep 1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Oct 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Jan 1965-Mar 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, Apr 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Budget, Costs, 1961-1965 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Specifications, Building Notes, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Specifications, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Specifications, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Space Analyses, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Meeting Minutes -- Administration, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Meeting Minutes -- Architects, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Meeting Minutes -- Architects, 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Meeting Minutes -- Geiringer (Engineers), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Jan 1963-May 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Jun 1963-Sep 1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Oct 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Jul 1964-Oct 1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Job Meeting Memoranda, Nov 1964-Feb 1965 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Progress Reports, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Progress Reports, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Wighton-Abbott -- Budget, Cost Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Wighton-Abbott -- Contracts, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Dedication -- Press Kit, Program, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- New Releases, Clippings, 1962-1965 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Warren Weaver Hall -- Floor Plans, Drawings [O], undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Mews -- General, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 1 Washington Mews [Ireland House], 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 3 Washington Mews, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 10 Washington Mews, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 12 Washington Mews, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 14 Washington Mews, 1971-1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 14A Washington Mews, 1963-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 15 Washington Mews, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 16 Washington Mews, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 48 Washington Mews, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - 52 Washington Mews, May 1966-Sep 1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 52 Washington Mews, Oct 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - 4-6 Washington Place, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 4-6 Washington Place, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 4-6 Washington Place, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - 4-6 Washington Place, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - 4-6 Washington Place -- Psychology Building (Proposed), undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - 7-10 Washington Place, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - 10 Washington Place -- Institute for Developmental Studies, 1966-1970 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - 15 Washington Place, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - 21 Washington Place, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - 21 Washington Place, Jan 1964-Aug 1964 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - 21 Washington Place, Sep 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - 21 Washington Place, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - 21 Washington Place, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square North -- Trees, 1974-1984 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - 1-6 Washington Square North -- General, Multiple Houses [O], 1962-1967 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - 1 Washington Square North, 1961-1970 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - 2 Washington Square North, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - 3 Washington Square North -- Social Work, General Education, Edward Hopper Studio, 1961-1977 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - 4 Washington Square North, 1962-1977 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - 5 Washington Square North, 1959-1964 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - 5 Washington Square North, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - 5 Washington Square North, 1978-1985, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - 6 Washington Square North, 1962-1986 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - 7-13 Washington Square North, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - 21 Washington Square North -- Inst. of African American Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - 22 Washington Square North -- Faculty Club, 1963-1985 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - 27 Washington Square North -- Center for Gifted Children, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - 50 Washington Square South -- Kevorkian Center Site; Brazilian, German House Sites (proposed), 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - 50 Washington Square South -- Kevorkian Center Site; Brazilian, German House Sites (proposed) -- Drawing, Floor Plans [O], undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - 51-53 Washington Sq. So. -- John Sloan & Inness Studios [O], 1934, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - 54 Washington Square South, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Washington Square Village, 1960-1966 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - 29 Washington Square West -- Penthouse, 1963-1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 32 Washington Square West, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse -- President's Office File, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse -- Zoning, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, Jan 1962-Aug 1962 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, Sep 1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, Oct 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, Apr 1963-Nov 1963 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 37 Washington Square West --President=s Penthouse--Plans Room, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 37 Washington Square West -- President=s Penthouse, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Waverly Building, 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Waverly Building, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Waverly Building, 1966-1967, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Waverly Building -- Music Room, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 18 Waverly Place, 1962-1966 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - 25 Waverly Place, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - 28-30 Waverly Place, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, Apr 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Weinstein/University Place Residence Hall, 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - 528-530 West Broadway -- School of the Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 29)